This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed to Navy Headquarters to rescue his brother Ace from execution.
Also determined to keep Ace alive is the notorious pirate Whitebeard,
who launches a surprise attack with his massive crew.
Gah!
Did he crack the air?
A sea quake!
He's turning the ocean waters against us!
Gah!
You...
I...
I won't lose.
You got some fight left.
Look, I'm not gonna kill you today, all right?
Don't fight it. You're too valuable to die in a place like this.
Run wild with us and our flight will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
Screw you, you old fart!
Tell me, why does everyone on this ship call him Pops?
You don't get it?
Because he calls us sons.
None of us have any family left. Hell, the whole world hates us.
So it's nice, right?
I know it's just a word, but it still feels nice.
The force that could destroy the world.
The power of the Tremor Tremor fruit.
The power of the Tremor
ING
bumps
The...
That's a lie!
You know the damn truth!
You told me not to go after him, but I wouldn't listen!
I'm your captain, and I told you to go.
Ace was only following my orders.
Isn't that right, Marco?
Yep, I heard it myself.
Then you left.
Sorry for all the trouble, really.
Teach broke the rules of our ship, and you had to seek justice.
Everyone in the world knows what happens if you mess with one of our crewmates.
If you do, you're gonna pay the price.
That means if anyone lays a finger on you, Ace, they're gonna have to deal with us!
Don't worry, Ace, we'll get you out of here!
Get ready to make hell your new home, Navy bastards!
Have to admit, we asked for this.
That had better not be regret, I hear.
This is a real mess.
All right, what do you say we tally up the odds?
On this side, we've got us warlords, the Navy's most ferocious weapons, the admirals, and a hundred thousand soldiers!
On that side, they've got the Whitebeard Pirates!
An entire fleet of more than 40 allied ships.
Okay, it's your move, Whitebeard. Let's go!
Oh, I like it.
Looks like you are gonna watch from the sideline.
I know. You're just here to kill some time.
More for me, then.
This is oppressive. I can hardly stand it.
These men are all the same. Disgusting, bloodthirsty beasts.
In all my travels, I've only met one exception.
Please stay safe, Luffy. For me.
The water! What's wrong?
It's receding. What's causing it?
What the hell is going on?
What's happening? Why is the ship moving backwards?
Oh, come on! We had this! What gives? It was nothing but smooth sailing two minutes ago!
I mean, it confuses you!
Campbell, you've got some of my favorite parts there!
Stupid ocean, we don't have time to go backward!
What's making this happen?
He's here.
What? And now it's over? I'm not complaining, but weird.
It pushed us! A good distance back.
Well, great! At this rate, by the time we get there, the fight will be over!
What was that?
Jinbei! Come on! Can we go faster? We're already late! We can't let them kill Ace!
Ace will be safe, for now. We'll get there.
Okay.
Give me a break!
What? You know something that we don't?
Is your fish man karate gonna get us there on time?
Or better yet, are you gonna get your pals the whale sharks to give us a ride?
My powers don't have much to offer here.
Yeah? Then where's that confidence coming from?
He says we'll make it, okay? So we're gonna make it!
He says we'll make it! It's that simple, huh?
Fine. You keep believing.
I'm taking a nap.
Wake me when we get there.
Uh, Captain Buggy? I really don't see this working out if we don't move any faster.
You're not giving up on your dream, are you? To become the king? It's destiny, right?
Oh, uh, yeah. Well, when the timing's right, I'm sure some kind of miracle will happen.
But this obviously ain't the right time, so all I can really do is wait.
So you are giving up? How can you let us down like that?
What's wrong with you? Can't you see?
Huh? Just look at him. That's not surrender. It's not laziness. That's confidence.
No, it's not. Not at all.
See? Cool as can be. He's perfectly composed. So regal he's like a king already.
How can I be so blind? You're right.
He's amazing!
So wrong. All of it.
I know miracles ain't exactly the most common of occurrences,
but what the hell else could I do except wait for one? Damn it.
The tide is changing course. We're moving forward again.
Did you do something?
Not me. All I've been doing is keeping us on course.
It feels like it's starting to pick up speed.
It's happening! He's right!
I know! What is it? What's going on?
Hey, Captain Buggy! It's happening just like you said!
Look! The miracle you prophesied!
What's going on? Huh?
It's just a coincidence.
I don't know what's going on, but it's our chance! Go!
What did I tell you guys? All you gotta do is wait for the right time!
And now that time is calling me to become the king!
You're incredible, Captain Buggy! One of a kind!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Yeah! At this rate, we'll make it for sure!
Hey! Behind us!
Oh, hell no!
I don't get it!
I don't get it! Nobody is moving!
Maybe they're just waiting for Whitebeard's command!
I'm choking on the tension!
What the? It reversed! The tide is rising again!
Look! The horizon!
What the? That's not right!
And here comes the final payoff!
That harmless sea quake he threatened us with earlier was just the prelude to a massive tsunami!
The Quake Man is what they call him! He wields the power of the Tremor Tremor Fruit!
The Tremor Tremor Fruit!
Our forces may be many, but that won't guarantee a victory! Not against Whitebeard at least!
Before him, before him, his crew, no one is safe! He has the power to destroy the world on his veins!
It's happening! The Great War!
Let's go!
Yeah!
The Invaders! 47 pirate ships from the new world led by Whitebeard!
The Defenders! The two greatest forces of the government!
Navy HQ! And the Seven Warlords!
No matter who wins, no matter who loses, the world will be forever changed!
Let's go!
Use thy solution!
Pいきます!
It's a Tsunami!
Now that is power.
He's straight out of hell.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
My sage.
Aokiji, you little squirt.
He froze it!
That was too close!
Kuzan saved our butts!
Artisan!
The whole bay is iced over!
The ship's locked in.
We can't even move.
Hey, come on, guys.
We've got the admirals on our side.
They're the Navy's greatest warriors, right?
Yeah, you're right.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Screw Whitebeard.
All cannons!
Open fire!
Save the Moby Dick!
Well, let's move.
We've got something to stand on now.
Let's show them what we can do, gentlemen!
We've got the commanders backing us up, too.
Open fire and give them everything you've got!
Round to camera offensive.
Right!
If I'm not mistaken, that's the fifth division commander, Flower Sword Vista!
Keep on your toes, Toshigi.
The commanders aren't the only ones we've got to worry about here.
Every one of these SOBs is a mighty soldier in his own right.
Yes, yes, thank you, sir.
This ice in the water ain't half bad.
Nice of him to set up some stationary targets for us.
Let's finish these ships off so we can invade the island.
Yeah, I'm not sure it's going to be that easy.
They're sending out the vice-admirals of Navy HQ.
It's a rare sight to see them all lined up in a row like that.
Ain't that cute?
It's like they rolled out a buster call to greet us.
Too bad.
Because this time we're the ones doing the busting,
as they're all about to find out.
Hey, Tsuru, why don't you stand back some?
Yeah, please, just leave this nonsense up to us.
Have a nice cup of tea.
Stay safe.
Don't give me that, you condescending pricks.
I'm fine.
Besides, there's no place safe now,
even if I swam all the way to the end of the sea.
We're setting anchor here on the ice, boys.
It's time to trounce those Navy sissies.
Now push for solid ground.
Go!
We're happy to give our lives for Pops.
It'd be an honor.
Bring it on, Navy.
My men got nothing to fear.
Enough talk.
Let's go!
Score, pirates!
Yeah!
Now, it all begins.
Oh, man!
Look!
Is Dracula and Mihawk gonna make a move?
Well, what do you know?
That is mighty strange.
So piqued his interest, did they?
Hawkeye, finally willing to fight.
You're gonna grace them with your sword for once.
That icy gaze would leave even a seasoned warrior frozen dead in his tracks.
Even with his blade resting upon his back.
Who has the courage to stare him down?
Hawkeye.
Every swordsman worth their salt longs to cross blades with him.
How else are we to find our worth but to do?
Climbing the steps of glory with death nipping at our heels.
Hey, that's the black sword.
Quite famous.
To be precise.
Huh?
It's named Night.
There are only 12 like it in the world.
They bear the highest grade.
See the dark edge of the blade?
The temper line?
Its clove pattern?
An ornate design suitable for only the greatest swordsman.
It's Hawkeye!
To be precise.
What are these?
The End
Mihawk and Kizaru launch an attack against Whitebeard.
Unfazed, his commanders leap into the fray,
showing off their fearsome Devil Fruit powers.
As the struggle rages on,
Admiral Aka'inu unleashes a living hell
that transforms the battlefield.
On the next One Piece,
an all-consuming Inferno,
Admiral Aka'inu's power!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!